So, Poop Squirt, remind us again why
we're here at the Hometown Buffet. My
aunts are in town this weekend. I can't
go on hiding them forever, so I figured
I might as well rip the band-aid off
now. Ew, gross. I don't want to meet
your ugly family. What if they smell
like you? I think it's just so sweet
that Scootaloo wants to introduce her
family to you, Rainbow Dash. It really
speaks to how much she cares about you.
Rarity, stop it. You saying that stuff
is what encourages [__] like this. I
don't want her ambushing my ass with
family meetups like I'm her surprise
date or some [__] Is Is that what this
feels like to you, Rainbow Dash?
Babies are so [__] lucky. They don't
ever got to pay for [__] Hey, [__]
How old are you? Three and a half.
Wrong answer. Try again. Two. That's the
ticket. Now you're thinking like a
champ.
Look good. There they are over there.
Let's go say hi to them. Why are they
sitting next to each other? That's kind
of gay. Yeah, it's making me so mad.
Every pony, this is my aunt Lofty. And
the huge one is Aunt Holiday. They take
care of me because my parents don't want
to. You're so fat. Why are you a fatty
fat [__] [__] You fat tub of lard.
Good god, you're fat. I can see why you
wanted this meet up to happen at the all
you can eat hometown buffet. Is there
anything left to eat? What? No. No. I
swear I've only been eating green beans.
Yeah, all you can eat green beans. Don't
think I don't see all the butter and
bacon bits cooked in. You're not fooling
any horse with those lumpy pancakes
slapped together on your
backside. I bet you wobble like uncooked
Pillsberry Doughboy biscuits when you
walk down the hall to drop a fat load in
the toilet, if you can even make it
there. And Lofty, what is it that you
see in Ant Holiday? I love thick [__]
[__] Makes their butts easier to
slap. Okay, where's my present? You
always bring me presents. Haha, of
course, Scootaloo. I got it right here.
Oh, I seem to have misplaced it. Did you
check under your flabs of
skin? Ah, here it is. It better be 2,000
Robux. 500 Robux. That's amazing, Scoo.
You can make one whole outfit with that.
Yeah, you'll be the talk of the server.
Well, now that every pony is here, why
don't we all get to know one another?
How do lesbians have sex? Pretty sure
being gay means hard pass at the gates.
What's it like knowing you're not going
to heaven? Why aren't Scooters real
parents here? Well, how can I put this
in a way that doesn't make us sound like
gay Philly diddlers? You see, some
parents are just more busy than others,
little girl. So, they entrusted us with
her care. They had a lot of problems,
and they didn't always treat Scooter
like how a kid should be treated. But
that's okay because even though
Scootaloo was an accident, we vowed to
always take care of her. What does she
mean, Rarity? Why is Scootaloo an
accident? It means she's unwanted and
undeserving of affection.
Why did you tell them that? I hate you.
Scoo, come back. I didn't mean to. It
just slipped out.
Hey kiddo, open the door. No, you're
just going to make fun of me. Now, why
would I ever do that? You know why? It's
because I was an accident.
Kid, I'm going to tell you something
that you never told anyone else.
The truth is I I was an accident, too.
My daddy thought he was just going to
bust a quick nut, then have a quick cold
one while watching Wheel of Fortune.
Then damn, Rainbow Baby. My mom was even
going to name me Oopsy Dashy. You know,
like Daisy, but my dad thought it was
stupid as [__] So, I didn't have a name
for a while until they settled on
Rainbow Dash when I head by the
Lightning Cloud at the age of two.
Thanks a lot, Rainbow Dash. I really
needed to hear that. Twilight. My
parents always told me they were
thrilled when I came along. But once
during Hearts Warming, my dad got drunk
as [__] and told me I was a surprise
baby. That's been a lifelong secret that
I never told anyone. Thanks for making
me feel better while I wipe my smelly
butt
cheeks. Hey, do you want to come eat
with me? No. Okay, I guess I'll be
seeing
you. Oh, you were in that one. Are you
done crying like a [__] Rainbow Dash,
is it true that you were an accident?
Lol. [__] no, [__] This rainbow ass
was expected, which makes me cool as
[__] you [__] loser. Come on, you
little
[__] Put that Hawaiian roll down,
you [__] But I like me some Hawaiian
rolls. Every pony does. It's our natural
instinct as horses to go for any wheat
product first. That's why they put it at
the front of the line. Bread is a waste
meant to fill you up so you don't get
your money's worth. I won't eat it then.
Anything to be like you, Rainbow Dash.
Look, [__] Eggs are packed with
protein, which will help you if you ever
get into a fight. But I don't get into
fights. I do. My plate is full. So, give
me your plate so I can put a bunch more
eggs on it. Look, Rarity. A lot of
rolls. I see that. Quick, grab as many
as you can and take them back to our
table. Big sis, look, they have waffles.
Go ahead and grab some. Will that really
be okay? Granny Smith hits me with a
belt anytime I try to eat stuff that
aren't apples. Well, that old prune
isn't here right now, is she? You're the
best. Big sister, Applejack. What kind
of older sister would I be if I told you
what you can and can't eat? A really bad
one like Rainbow Dash. Apple Bloom.
Shush. She'll hear
you. What the hell, Rainbow Dash? I
heard what your sister was saying about
me. Applejack, don't hit her.
Sweet Celestia, you don't tell me what
to do. Rarity, give me some Hawaiian
rolls. No, you took all of them. You
were up there first. You could have
grabbed some. That's not going to make
me give you one. That one's not even my
sister. Don't pull my arm.
Stop it, disgusting fat [__]
What are you doing? Oh, Rainbow Dash,
you startled me. It's It's nothing
really. I picked up food reviewing as a
hobby. The fudge? Yeah, I go around the
latest hotspots and post my reviews on
my blog. I know it's silly. Yeah, it
sounds super gay and stupid. Well, I I
took it up cuz, you know, I don't really
have much going on on Sundays. It's not
even Sunday. It's Friday evening. You
look like a total loser eating all by
yourself. You should be embarrassed.
Now, what kind of pony do you think you
are to be judging me? A pony who's
right. I don't have to take this from
you. Then take it from the Ass Blaster
3000 instead. Excuse
me. There are plenty of other tables in
this buffet that I can sit at so we
don't have to look at each other. Good
day. What was that about Rainbow
Darling? She's sitting alone like some
loser who does that. Gross. She brought
her iPad with her to the buffet and
everything. Some pony should call the
waitress over so we can have her thrown
out.
Jesus [__] Christ, girl. Get to the
[__]
point. Your food reviews suck. You need
to
stop. Please understand, I am new to
food reviews. If you have any tips, it
would be much appreciated.
Here's a tip. Stop. I don't have to
post. These are views, you know.
Reviews.
I'm doing this for fun. Doesn't matter.
Still sucks. Don't you get embarrassed
eating alone like some [__] ass loser?
Um, for your information, I am not a
loser. And I am not by myself. Do you
really think I would be alone on a
Friday evening? I am actually having a
great meal with all of my friends. Thank
you very much.
Damn, I hate to see her come, but I sure
do love to see her go.
Rarity, is Scuta going to be okay?
Sweetie, I really don't care. Can you
just like not talk to me for 30 minutes
and leave me alone? Did I do something
wrong again? Oh, no. You just have a
really punchable face.
Hey, sweetie Belle, would you mind
getting down on your hands and knees for
a second? Oh my god, Scoo is going to
[__] me. She's going to stake her claim
right here, right now with every pony
watching by using her overwhelming,
unstoppable brain melting dominance and
muscular physique to crush my soul into
a giggling puddle of Philly
goo. Thanks, [__] I couldn't reach the
gummy
bears. Hey, Scoots. When are you going
to introduce us to your parents like
your real mom and dad?
Bro, why is Scoo hanging from the
ceiling? Is your sister mentally
challenged, love? She's not hanging from
the ceiling. She's hanging from the
ceiling fan. Cut her down now. Babies
aren't supposed to hang upside
down. No, it's funny. Yes, it is
humorous to tie her up there and let her
dangle like a [__] ball sack because
she's unable to fly. So, forcing her to
hang from there is like a constant
reminder of what she will never be able
to do on her own, which is fly because
she's disabled. That is really mean.
It's no wonder her first word was
calling you a [__] and your wife a
[__] No, we just told you it's funny.
Now shut the [__] up and help me pack
for our trip to the Amazon rainforest.
The [__] Scooteroo was just born 2 days
ago. You think I don't know that? Get
this. If we leave fast enough, she'll
forget we even existed. And then we can
go on adventures forever without being
tied down to a baby.
I can't believe you both. This is your
own daughter. A Pegasus that can't fly
will never survive a day in the Amazon
rainforest. What is it with you and the
Amazon rainforest?
Going to the Amazon rainforest is more
fun than changing a diaper full of [__]
There's some food in the fridge that got
delivered from Door Dash. I pray to God
that you didn't eat it all again, you
fat lesbian
[__] Move out of the way, Tubby. Move
now before I make you. No. See, you not
moving proves that I'm right. Father and
mother were right about you. You have no
self-control. Our family lineage is
[__] And the only thing that calls to
me now is adventure. Just as powdered
donuts and three cheese, garlic bread
calls to your fat ass.
Let's go, dear. The taxi is waiting.
Oh my god. Will you shut up?
change.
Damn, that sucks. Big sweaty balls.
Wow, I had no idea your life was so
pitiful. Sprinkle tits. And your parents
sound like major bullies. And I hate
bullies almost as much as I love fat
asses. Bullies are the worst.
Put that Hawaiian roll down, you [__]
Stop it, disgusting fat [__]
Wait here, Apple Bloom. I need to go
somewhere. It's Scoo. And where are you
going? I am going to make things right.
I didn't ask what you were doing. I
asked where you were going.
Hey, uh, Twilight, how's the food blog
coming along? Oh, that I I don't really
do that stuff anymore. Oh, why? Some
pony was just leaving nasty comments
about me on my blog, and I realized
maybe there were some valid points in
what they were saying. You shouldn't
listen to what random no pony [__]
say about you online. You know, ponies
who complain about things they don't
like are the real losers cause. You
know, they could be literally anywhere
else and they choose to waste their own
time trying to make you feel bad because
you're having more fun than they are.
Them and their talentless asses. That's
whack. If you ask me, I think your blog
is really cool. You You really think so?
Well, I suppose I can continue posting
on my blog if you really think that way.
Hey, [__] Me and the girls are going
to Scootaloo's house to eat Little
Caesars next. They have a special
limited edition Mountain Dew flavor that
you can only get from them. It's called
Mango Rush and tastes like mango or some
[__] Do you maybe want to come hang
with us and get content for your blog?
Limited edition, huh? I'd hate to be a
clout chaser, but if you insist.
Hey, Twilight. Want to take a
commemorative selfie together to
celebrate the Mountain Dew and Little
Caesars's crossover?
Told you I got friends.
Suck it.
Haha. You two look really cute together.
Are you a couple?
Oh no. Scooter's mom and daddy are back
on their banana bikes. Um, these aren't
called banana bikes. Banana bikes sound
gay. These are our speed cycles which we
use to get around really fast. We are
here to pick up our baby and take her
back to the Amazon rainforest where we
built a treehouse to live together as a
family. Now that Scooter is old enough
to fly, she can fly up into trees to
pick bananas and [__] for us like some
little ugly banana retrieving monkey.
Your daughter is disabled. You stupid
pieces of [__] You're her mom. You
don't even know. Well, maybe I forgot
because I don't care about her
emotionally. She is still old enough to
survive the wilderness and thus can
scavenge the grounds for seeds and
berries and fend off tigers and large
monkeys. She is not going with you. We
won't allow it as her guardians.
We are her legal parents. I literally
pushed her out of my [__] Come over
and put her in the back of one of our
banana bikes or we are calling the cops.
Hey, so I don't know who you two are or
who they are or what the [__] is going
on, but I do know I don't want the cops
to come here because both me and Rainbow
Dash have warrants. If Scootaloo is not
your baby, you have to let her go. We
will let Scooter decide.
Wow. [__] wow. I can't believe this.
After all the things we've done for that
[__] If this is what Scooter chooses,
then so be it. I'm sorry, sweetie Bell.
Apple Bloom. But at the end of the day,
these are still my mommy and daddy. So,
does this mean the days of the Rainbow
Dash fan club are over? No. It will
still be up and running. Just a party of
one, me out in the Amazon rainforest,
worshiping Rainbow Dash all alone. I can
tell you two were never that into it
anyway. Yeah, that's true. Aunt Lofty,
can you be a bad [__] and go grab me my
lunchbox? The one with Rainbow Dash on
the cover. Of of course, dear. Anything
for you.
What are you waiting for, [__] Put
that lunchbox in the back of either me
or your dad's speed cycle. It's a long
way back to the Amazon rainforest, and
you're walking. Wait, can you open it
for me? I think it's stuck. Whatever.
We didn't doubt you for a second.
Squirt. Something tells me they won't be
coming back anytime
soon. The seasons come and go like
thoughts of
you. Like a wave returns to the sea into
the blue.
may change but in a
cycle that I can't
lose each painful but
delightful to live
through. You came into my life just like
another season. Not for long, just a
time. Just like another season. Maybe
this time next year you'll reappear for
no reason. But I'll cherish every day
until you find my way this season.
The seasons turn and change just like
your
mind. Like the sun gives into the moon
into the night.
Time continues marching. It slowly
crawls. With each new one
starting, I
recall you came into my life. Just like
another season. Not for long, just a
time. Just like another season. Maybe
this time next year you'll reappear for
no reason. But I'll cherish every day
until you find my way this season.
Oh, this
season. Each time of year carries
memories like a never fading whisper in
the
breeze. Oh, we will keep on
changing all over
again. Yeah, we will keep on
changing just like another season. Don't
want to
know by the heart
season another season.